Can I speak to you?
Yes, sir, you can speak to me.
Are you ready to give your child to somebody?
Yes, sir.
SCOAN Sunday Service
I see somebody living inside you.
Come.
SCOAN Sunday Service
You are two. There is a demon that is trying to destroy your life, claiming to be your husband.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Look here!
Come here!
Before I count two you must be here. One, two.
Stand up!
Come here!
Who are you?
Leave me alone.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave me alone. T.B. Joshua, leave me alone.
You've been disturbing me. Since I came here,
you've been disturbing me. Leave me alone.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I should leave you alone?
I have told you. She belongs to me. Leave me alone.
I said leave me alone. Can't you hear? She belongs to me.
Everything – mine, mine.
Who?
I say it's mine. I am her husband.
Who is your husband?
She is my wife.
He is your husband?
Me?
You've been disturbing me since I came here.
Who is inside you?
I am her husband now.
He is your husband?
Who is he?
I had her since… But that man she married,
that praying man, always giving me trouble like that.
The man will not rest – prayer, prayer, prayer, prayer, prayer.
I nearly killed her the last time, car accident.
Where is your husband?
Why is this man disturbing me?
This is the thing, that we married since. When we went to the water,
we did an agreement and we did wedding. We had children.
Suddenly, she carried a Bible – born again, born again, born again.
That man she married – prayer, prayer, prayer, prayer.
Where is he?
The man is in the US, I am telling you.
So, you came from the US?
So, he is a prayer warrior?
Too much.
SCOAN Sunday Service
He will not let me, the true husband, stay.
I said leave my wife to come back. He refused.
Since he married my queen, no progress. His finances…
You locked him.
Are you joking with me? She's my queen. Can't you see her?
She is my queen.
Let her go.
Let her go, T.B. Joshua, let her go.
I should have got rid of her last time. Every time she's pregnant - accident, accident, accident.
Come, give me your hand.
No.
Give me your hand.
No, you won't deceive me. You will take my power.
You will take my power.
What are you doing here? Give me space.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come here.
You will take my power.
Watch your screen.
FIRE! In the name of Jesus Christ.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen.
It is one of the visitors from the US.
FIRE all over your body, in the name of Jesus!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave me alone.
FIRE all over your body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Stand up.
One, two.
Your hands up.
Who is Jesus?
He is Lord.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Watch your screen.
See what is coming out of her.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Your back on the floor.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank you, Lord.
In Jesus' name, she is free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
She doesn’t know how she got there.
SCOAN Sunday Service
See what is happening.
She is shy.
SCOAN Sunday Service
She has now come to her real self.
What happened?
Man of God? Good afternoon, sir.
Good afternoon, sir.
What do you say?
Man of God. God bless you, sir.
What happened?
I don’t know. What happened?
I was sitting there, I think you came and I touched you.
I don’t know what else happened.
I was sitting there, beside her.
Where is your child? Your daughter?
Where is she?
Sir, that's my baby.
What brought you here?
I don’t know. I was sitting down there.
What happened to you?
Me?
I don’t know. I was sitting with my child.
What happened?
You don't know what happened?
No, I know I was sitting there. Man of God - I think you came that way.
I don't know...
Why are you greeting me 'Good afternoon'?
It is a pleasure, sir, to meet you.
And you have abused me.
You call me: "T.B. Joshua, what has happened to me?"
Me?
You want to slap me?
No, Man of God, please, sorry, sir. I'm so sorry, sir.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Watch your screen.
I don't behave like this. Not me.
People who know me will tell that I am "soft-spoken". I don't even...
What do you say?
I am soft-spoken, I don’t talk too much.
Testimony Time
My name is Ada, I am from the United States of America.
My experience here has been absolutely wonderful, amazing, marvellous.
A lot of breakthrough in my life.
For example, this morning during the first service,
I was delivered from a mermaid spirit and set free.
It was a marvellous deliverance today and I know
my life will never be the same because, as the man of God says, our past is over.
My past is really over today.
The experience I had here today was just absolutely fantastic and I will never ever forget it.
After the prayer, it was as if something left my body, something left my stomach.
I just felt it go out, and I feel free, happier, relaxed.
I feel definitely free and lighter since the deliverance today.
I say to people out there, this is real.
The man of God is real. There is nothing fake about it.
The power of God is actually here, alive and well.
I have seen it, I have tasted it, I have experienced it today
and I really thank God today for that experience.
Believe God, trust God and God will do the same that He's done for me in your lives.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ. Amen.
We pray to God that your deliverance and your freedom will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 25/06/2018